(harmonizing):
♪ Thor and Dr. Jones ♪
♪ One plays with lightning ♪
♪ The other plays with bones. ♪
(Howard:)Oh, man, that rocks.
(Raj:)Hey, remember
The Ark of the Covenant?
(Howard:)Yeah?
(Raj:)That's how much we're
gonna melt people's faces off.
(Sheldon:)I appreciate your interest
in the apartment.
(Sheldon:)I just need to ask you
a few standard questions.
(Bernadette:)Sure.
It says here you're a chemist.
(Sheldon:)Which element
on the periodic table
(Sheldon:)do you feel is too big
for its britches?
(Bespectacled Man:)Is that supposed to be a joke?
(Sheldon:)Looks like argon's not
the only one
(Sheldon:)with an attitude problem.
(Sheldon:)In general,
(Sheldon:)would you say
that you smell better, worse
(Sheldon:)or the same as you do right now?
(Sheldon:)I was going to ask you
(Sheldon:)what is the best fruit,
(Sheldon:)but then I realized
what I want to ask you
(Sheldon:)is why is there a Band-Aid
on your forearm,